Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive,
- Series IX. Music collection
  - 12 inch vinyl
    - Renegades of Rhythm Tour
      - Greatest hits, 1984; SR-6913; Sugar Hill Gang (Musical group) (Box 6)
        Fiesta; African Record Centre distributors
        Brookly, New York
      - Bounce, rock, skate, roll, 1979; SR-6914; Mason, Vaughan. (Box 6)
      - Rap, bounce, rockskate; Western gangster town, 1980; SR-6915; Trickeration (Musical group) (Box 6)
      - Get up and dance; You've just got to be the one, 1979; SR-6916-SR-6917; Freedom (Musical group: Jackson, Miss.) (Box 6)
      - Flash it to the beat; Fusion beats vol. 2, 1982; SR-6918 (Box 6)
        Side A recorded live and A "Tactic Mark Production"--Label._x000D_ Side A is a bootleg from a show at Bronx River Centre featuring Flash manually operating a drum machine while the Furious Five rhyme over the top. It was released without Flash's knowledge
      - Flash it to the beat; Fusion beats vol. 2, 1980; SR-6919 (Box 6)
      - Cut Chemist suite: featuring hip hop remixes., 1998; SR-6920 (Box 6)
        Sahara Records
      - Love in the morning; Dub in the morning, 1980; SR-6921; Sibbles, L. (Leroy) (Box 6)
      - Prop-master's party!!, 1989; SR-6922 (Box 6)
        T.K. Disco: Distributed by T.K. Productions
      - Beat, 1981; SR-6925; Trouble Funk (Musical group) (Box 6)
      - Last message, 1960-1969; SR-6926 disc1; X, Malcolm, 1925-1965. (Box 6)
        Micmac Records
      - Funkadelic, 1975; SR-6927; Funkadelic (Musical group) (Box 6)
        Jam Records
      - Iron leg: the complete Mickey and the Soul Generation., 2002; SR-6928; Mickey and the Soul Generation (Musical group) (Box 6)
        Charisma Records; All Platinum Records
        S.l. Englewood, New Jersey
      - Unity, 1984; SR-6929; Afrika Bambaataa, 1957- (Box 6)
        Cali-Tex Records
      - Mustapha Tettey Addy: master drummer from Ghana., 1972; SR-6930 (Box 6)
      - Mr. Jaws and other fables, 1975; SR-6931; Goodman, Dickie. (Box 6)
        Tangent
      - Magi'x wand, 2000; SR-6932; DJ Magicut. (Box 6)
        Cash Records: Distributed by Private Stock Records
      - It's hell, 1974; SR-6933 disc 2; Brown, James, 1933-2006. (Box 6)
      - Stand!, 1969; SR-6934; Sly & the Family Stone (Musical group) (Box 6)
      - Blind over you, 1975; SR-6937; Chicago Gangsters (Musical group) (Box 6)
      - Try to hold on (disco version), 1975; SR-6938; Moore, Bobby, 1930-2006. (Box 6)
        Matrix / Runout (Both Sides Runout Etchings): DT 62252-1A TM/JR.
        Gold Mink Records
      - J.B., 2000; SR-6939-SR-6940; Brown, James, 1933-2006. (Box 6)
        Scepter Records
      - Wattstax: the living word., 1973; SR-6974 (Box 20)
      - Bambaata beats, 1983; SR-6889; Afrika Bambaataa, 1957- (Box 104)
        Hand written sticky note on jacket: "Paydirt: sample edits disc of breaks rare + unrare."_x000D_
      - Beat, 1981; SR-8985-8986; Trouble Funk (Musical group) (Box 460)
      - Blind over you, 1975; SR-6956; Chicago Gangsters (Musical group) (Box 461)
        Gold Plate Records
      - Candido's drum fever., 1973; SR-9031; Candido, 1921- (Box 461)